<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aspergers on Jeffreys Ruminations</title>
    <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/aspergers/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aspergers on Jeffreys Ruminations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/aspergers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Living In My World</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/aspergers/living-in-my-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/aspergers/living-in-my-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was browsing reddit like I am prone to do now-a-days and came across a picture that completely captures me in social settings:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-4jktXxEAxM4/TtGkI5x8jTI/AAAAAAAAAK4/_pD0mWiIDeg/s400/cartoon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Me At Parties&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who have been with me at parties - there are typically two ways that I respond.  I show up long enough to be spotted and then quietly and discretely leave without telling anyone, or I blend with the walls and pretty much hide.  This was very evident at one of the wedding showers I attended for Stephen/Danielle&amp;rsquo;s wedding this past March.  Why do I do this?  I&amp;rsquo;m usually completely overwhelmed and my brain shuts down.  Thus I do the two things that will bring me relief.  This is also why I do not allow parties to be thrown on my behalf - It&amp;rsquo;s hard to escape a party when you are the center of attention and I would be so mentally exhausted that it may sometimes make me physically ill.  Before my Asperger&amp;rsquo;s diagnosis, I thought this was entirely social anxiety and shyness - but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t explain the mental exhaustion toll that social interactions may cause me.  But now I understand why I respond in this way and I need to work on how to help solve this problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Small groups are easy (6-8 people).  Technical meetings are OK for me at almost any size.  But social gatherings are very very difficult.  This explains why I tried to hide when I used to attempt to go to my &amp;ldquo;mid-sized&amp;rdquo; small group at church.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you see me like this, you can understand why I&amp;rsquo;m doing this.  It isn&amp;rsquo;t a sign that I&amp;rsquo;m dissing you.  It&amp;rsquo;s just means I must escape to my &amp;ldquo;happy zone&amp;rdquo; from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Credit to &lt;a href=&#34;http://aspiestrategy.blogspot.com/&#34;&gt;Aspie Strategy&lt;/a&gt; blog for the image)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asperger Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/aspergers/aspergers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/aspergers/aspergers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, It has been a while since I have posted.  Many things have taken place since the start of this year, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The start of a new semester at school.  I am taking Data Structures (C+ + ), Discrete Mathematics 2, and Assembly Language (MIPS-32).  I may be on par to finish my certificate by the end of this year, then off to get a MS degree starting next year (while working full-time at that point).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve regressed on my blood clot.  My INR has been down lately for no reason that I can see.  So I&amp;rsquo;m on a frequent testing rotation until it gets stable.  My urological issue remains unsteady, but I feel it will always be undecided on how I&amp;rsquo;m doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week I visited the counseling center at school and took a battery of psychological tests. Apparently I suffer from a form of high functional autism called Asperger&amp;rsquo;s Syndrome.  Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve read the different symptoms of this syndrome, it is very obvious that I meet most of the symptoms and have met them throughout my life (even using the new not-yet-to-be-published DSM-V guidelines).  For most people, this type of diagnosis can be a crushing blow.  In my case, I have had to learn how to accommodate the difference in the way that my brain is wired and have learned  how to interact in a bare-minimum fashion with other people.  As such, the diagnosis was a relief to me in that I now understand many of the weird idiosyncrasies that I shared with no one else that I knew.For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know what the base symptoms of Asperger&amp;rsquo;s Syndrome, it can be basically broken down to having several of the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limited empathy towards others (It&amp;rsquo;s not that I don&amp;rsquo;t have empathy, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen automatically)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsteady gait, balance, coordination issues&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lack of noticing verbal and non-verbal clues from others&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communications difficulties with other (i.e., due to taking most concepts literally, not being able to look at people in the eyes, not picking up social cues in conversations, etc)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intense interest in certain topics, especially those dealing with math, science, engineering, and technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Detail oriented - Finding details/patterns or arriving at especially unique solutions to problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late Speech Development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dislike physical contact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extremely good long term memory, terrible short term memory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Difficulty in reading emotions in others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many more symptoms, but these are the key ones in my diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many online quizzes out there that can give you a quick analysis, but still you need a professional analysis to be sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, my score on the most comprehensive of the tests is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Aspie score: 170 of 200&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your neurotypical (non-autistic) score: 25 of 200&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are very likely an Aspie&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://rdos.net/eng/Aspie-quiz.php&#34;&gt;Aspie Quiz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.jeffreyrandow.org/images/asperger.png&#34; alt=&#34;My Asperger Chart&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess that is it for now.  I have two concerts that I need to process and post, but that will be next weekend at the earliest.  Have a great week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>