<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Walking on Jeffreys Ruminations</title>
    <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/walking/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Walking on Jeffreys Ruminations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/walking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2014 Fitness Summary</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/may-2014-fitness-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/may-2014-fitness-summary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my summary posting of my May 2014 fitness activities.  Most of my workouts and tracking is available on the main page of this website under the Fitness Log tab.  This contains my Walk/Jogging activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the month of May, I tracked that I walked or jogged approximately 30 miles in monitored activities (i.e., I did a planned walking/jogging workout;  this does not include the incidental walking that I do during the day).  This 30 miles were a part of 19 separate workouts.  The most I walked in 1 day was &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mapmyrun.com/workout/576023697&#34;&gt;2.38 miles on May 19&lt;/a&gt;.  The least was the logged 0.65 miles from May 29 when I was walking around the downtown of Grapevine in the middle of the day.  It was more a sightseeing log than an actual workout.  The area around my hotel was rather dangerous so I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to do any other outings when I was in Dallas at the end of May.  Note also that all of these walks/runs except for the 29th also includes my dog Rudy.  So I am a bit slowed by him at time when he stops to pee on everything and to smell every fence post/mailbox/etc on the path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this time, I changed from Endomondo to MapMyRun and acquired a bluetooth 4 heart rate sensor that I use to check my exertion level.  I also acquired running shoes because walking shoes don&amp;rsquo;t seem to cut it anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting towards the end of May, I started working out again at the gym (LA Fitness in San Antonio) working on primarily upper arm strength.  I also do a little bit of cardio depending on the availablity of machines (I did a 4 mile per hour run for 5 minutes on a treadmill or 6 floors of stairs on the Stairmaster).  Gym is still a little intimidating and I don&amp;rsquo;t like when there are a lot of people in the locker room because I am very self conscious in my appearance.  I need to learn the &amp;ldquo;DGAF&amp;rdquo; technique that peers have encouraged on Reddit or Nerd Fitness.  This week I plan to do some of the water fitness activities - just walking laps in the pool will help build up more muscle because of the resistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the gym front, I&amp;rsquo;m weighing the thought to join ResoluteFit when they open because some of their services could be beneficial to me.  My problem is that I think I also need the gym in San Antonio so that I can workout after work.  Once I get home, the only thing that I normally do is to walk.  It is very hard to motivate me to go to somewhere like Planet Fitness to workout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the weight side, I will make a comparison to the end of March/beginning of April 2014 since I have accurate data only to that point.  The first scale I bought is very off at times and will sometimes give me weights up to 5 pound different every time I use it.  So out it went and I went back to my old scale which was consistent.  Since March, I have gone from 398 down to 378 +/- a pound or two depending on what clothes I&amp;rsquo;m wearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have not had my A1C recalculated yet, so no comparison there.  I will have the test results back on June 11 when I have my next doctor appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it for now.  Thanks for keeping up with me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>