<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Old-network-blogs on Jeffreys Ruminations</title>
    <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Old-network-blogs on Jeffreys Ruminations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Blog Assimilated</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/network-blog-assimilated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/network-blog-assimilated/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have made a few huge updates today to the website.  Besides the tweaking of the overall look, I have assimilated my Network Blog postings onto the new Jekyll blog and will post about both on here.  I brought most of the posts from the former site here - but I did do some &amp;ldquo;Spring Cleaning&amp;rdquo; by removing ones that were time-related (webchats and so forth) and kept the old URL if possible.  There have been a few changes, however:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The URL &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.networkblog.net&amp;quot;&#34;&gt;http://www.networkblog.net&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; will redirect to this site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The feed URL for just the network blog is now &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jeffreyrandow.org/netblog.xml&amp;quot;&#34;&gt;http://jeffreyrandow.org/netblog.xml&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can access just the network blog postings by browsing to &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jeffreyrandow.org/netblog/&amp;quot;&#34;&gt;http://jeffreyrandow.org/netblog/&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why the change?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jekyll is awesome and I can stop worrying about security issues with Wordpress (it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a problem, but I wanted to be a bit more secure).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The site is hosted on Github (Github Pages) and other content is served by a variety of CDNs (Content Delivery Networks).  Thus I can post big files and use the Google CDN to serve the file in lieu of my old cable modem connection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permanence.  Keeping the files here provides a sense of permanence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s Coming?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, at work, I am currently in a middle of a big (huge for us) deployment of new laptops to all staff.  I plan to post some of the MDT and WDS tidbits I&amp;rsquo;ve learned.  (the deployment was on Windows 8.1 on the new boxen and Windows 7 on the old)  I&amp;rsquo;m also looking into an awesome networking security product that is free (PacketFence).  I&amp;rsquo;m also going to post my code for a MAPI utility that you can use to add a mailbox into someone&amp;rsquo;s Outlook Profile as a part of a logon script.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Script:  Missing X500 Email Addresses (IMCEAEX Errors)</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/useful-script-missing-x500-email-addresses-imceaex-errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/useful-script-missing-x500-email-addresses-imceaex-errors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a useful Powershell Script for fixing X500 Email address issues on Exchange boxen...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.righthandedexchange.com/2013/02/fixing-imceaex-ndrs-missing-x500.html&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TrueCrypt Possible Hacking Technique</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/truecrypt-possible-hacking-technique/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/truecrypt-possible-hacking-technique/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The guys over at The Invisible Things Lab have posted a possible attack vector on Truecrypt volumes using a modified bootloader that could possibly capture the volume password.  If you have a computer that can boot (or be set to boot) from USB or if it has a possible accessible hard drive (my computer has neither), then it is possible for a hacker who has physical access to a box to possibly compromise it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take it as you may...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-default&#34; size=&#34;large&#34; link=&#34;http://theinvisiblethings.blogspot.com.au/2009/10/evil-maid-goes-after-truecrypt.html&#34;&gt;TrueCrypt Hacking Technique&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Forensics Puzzle Contest</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/network-forensics-puzzle-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/network-forensics-puzzle-contest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While browsing the discussion board concerning a particular security conference currently underway today in Las Vegas, I came across an interest contest site that could be excellent in helping build ones forensic skills - The Network Forensics Puzzle Contest.  They have a contest currently underway at the said conference that hasn&#39;t been posted to the website, but it will be posted at a later time.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, the contest involves you analyzing a hard drive image and a network packet capture and find the answers to a series of questions based on what you find.  Skills involved can include (but are not limited to) packet analysis, crypto, protocol analysis, dump file analysis, and even some rudimentary programming.  It seems like it could provide a good challenge or contest for a network security group (or groups) to hone ones skill.  Most of it is still over my head at this time, but I expect that I could probably do a much better job towards the end of the year when I get nitty-gritty into Network Communication and Security at school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on the Network Forensics Puzzle Contest, click on the button below:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-default&#34;  size=&#34;large&#34; link=&#34;http://forensicscontest.com&#34;&gt;Forensics Contest&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S., while browsing the site and looking at Puzzle # 10, I found an &#34;interesting&#34; security podcast that I&#39;m going to start following:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-default&#34;  size=&#34;large&#34; link=&#34;http://pauldotcom.com/&#34;&gt;PaulDotCom Security Podcast Blog&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools:  IPV6 Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/tools-ipv6-toolbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/tools-ipv6-toolbox/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, here is my second round of tools.  This time it is for diagnostics and security of IPV6 connections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;alert type=&#34;error&#34; heading=&#34;Warning!&#34;&gt;These files are source-based so they need to be compiled by a C compiler (gcc, etc).  These files are intended to be compiled and run on a UNIX/Linux system.&lt;/alert&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-default&#34; type=&#34;primary&#34; size=&#34;large&#34; link=&#34;http://ipv6securitylab.org/&#34;&gt;Tool Information&lt;/button&gt;.  &lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-default&#34; type=&#34;success&#34; size=&#34;large&#34; link=&#34;http://ipv6securitylab.org/ipv6toolbox.html&#34;&gt;Download Tool&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tool:  Cuckoo Sandbox (Malware Analysis Tool)</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/tool-cuckoo-sandbox-malware-analysis-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/tool-cuckoo-sandbox-malware-analysis-tool/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, today&#39;s first tool came from Blackhat Conference underway right now.  Note that this isn&#39;t a &#34;blackhat&#34; tool - it is a diagnostic tool for any investigator to determine exactly what a particular malware does - by tracking the following (from the Cuckoo Sandbox homepage):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Native functions and Windows API calls traces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copies of files created and deleted from the filesystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dump of the memory of the selected process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Screenshots of the desktop during the execution of the malware analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network dump generated by the machine used for the analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tool runs under a Linux system of some type (the installation manual recommends Ubuntu) and requires that you use a virtualization system with it (KVM, VirtualBox, etc).  Will this entire system run as a VM guest?  I&#39;m not sure on that one yet and I haven&#39;t set up my home lab to test a scenario like that as of yet..  It works fine running locally on my system and using VBox.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;button type=&#34;button&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-default&#34; type=&#34;primary&#34; size=&#34;large&#34; link=&#34;href=&#34;http://www.cuckoosandbox.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Tool Information&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warning:  Update VirtualBox before Upgrading to Mountain Lion</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/warning-update-virtualbox-before-upgrading-to-mountain-lion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/warning-update-virtualbox-before-upgrading-to-mountain-lion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Note to the wise:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are upgrading to Mac OS X Mountain Lion, make sure that your copy of VirtualBox is up-to-date.  If it isn&#39;t, and if you are running a VBoxHeadless session to start a VM at login, you will be in a boot loop as the Mac will bugcheck and do a soft reboot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s why if you visited my weather website this afternoon and didn&#39;t see up-to-date information - my VBoxHeadless instance running my XP VM (for the Weather Station software) was causing a reboot.  All is fixed now.  :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experiences with HyperV and Linux</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/my-experiences-with-hyperv-and-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/my-experiences-with-hyperv-and-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I thought I would post a few tidbits about my recent experience with HyperV and various Linux distributions.  As some of you know, I self host my websites on my Windows 2008 R2 server at my house.  In the past 6 months or so, I have rotated through many different linux distributions to host my websites, but each attempt ended with abject failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have tried the following combinations of distributions and HyperV extensions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ubuntu 9.04 using the Microsoft HyperV extensions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ubuntu 9.10 using the 2.6.32 kernel modules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ubuntu 10.04 using the 2.6.32 kernel modules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debian Lenny using the 2.6.32 kernel modules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CentOS 5.4 using the Microsoft HyperV extension v2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CentOS 5.4 using the Microsoft HyperV extension v2.1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debian Lenny without using any extensions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CentOS 5.4 without using any extensions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ubuntu 9.04 without using any extensions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these were running the 64-bit version of the operating system, but I also tried a 32-bit version to the same avail.  Each attempt ended with a system failure (kernel_hung_task) usually after about 2~3 days.  This is running on hardware that can handle a full Windows 2008 R2 load or an individual Linux install with no hiccups.  I allocated each VM 100 GB hard drive partition, the synthetic NIC device (on those running extensions, otherwise the legacy NIC was used), and 3 GB of RAM.  The systems that did not exhibit the kernel_hung_task error just stopped functioning in a hung state without any logging of any type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Running VMWare, Virtual PC, or VirtualBox works just fine - other than the inconvenience of having to use an application type of virtualization versus a hypervisor-based system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So where does that leave me?  I no longer use HyperV for running Linux boxen.  HyperV works wonderfully for Windows-based systems and (much) earlier Linux builds (i.e., I&#39;m running a Fedora Core 9 box at work for spam filtering that has no hiccups, but running a Fedora 12 box causes the system hang issues).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TCPIP Fundamentals E-Book</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/tcpip-fundamentals-e-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/tcpip-fundamentals-e-book/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been waiting a bit too long to update here and missed a few things...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, Joseph Davies (aka &#34;The Cable Guy&#34; on Technet) has released the entire TCP/IP Fundamentals for  Microsoft Windows in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.microsoft.com/downloads/details.aspx?FamilyID=c76296fd-61c9-4079-a0bb-582bca4a846f&amp;amp;displaylang=en&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for the ebook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More to come later today or early tomorrow...&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Vista Networking Tips</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/quick-vista-networking-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/quick-vista-networking-tips/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After spending the past two months wading through the Vista Networking public newsgroup over at msnews.microsoft.com, I have come up with the following tips that will save the users from many problems:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.  If you are having network access/connectivity issues AND you have a Norton or McAfee network security (not AV, but I won&#39;t go there on that one) product, your issue is more than likely the Norton or McAfee product.  I haven&#39;t been answering these questions as I made a conscious decision years ago to never let either of these software manufacturers near any computer system I own/manage.  However, there have been countless posts in which Norton/McAfee security products are either blocking communications altogether, or have otherwise made networking the PC&#39;s virtually impossible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.  Make sure you disable network autotuning to get faster file copying/network access to other workgroup/domain computers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is easy, though.  Run the following command from a Command Prompt as an administrator:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;netsh int tcp set global autotuninglevel=disabled&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;netsh int tcp set global rss=disabled&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.  If you can&#39;t enable sharing, make sure that you have identified your network as Private.  If it is unidentified or Public, you will not be able to enable sharing (without hacking).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would hazard to guess that these three issues probably represent about 50% of the issues on an average day. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want Multiple Outlook Sessions at one time?</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/want-multiple-outlook-sessions-at-one-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/want-multiple-outlook-sessions-at-one-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is from a mailing list that I am on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, without further adieu, we are proud to present you with our &#34;ExtraOutlook&#34; tool that allows you to launch as many Outlook instances as you want. All you have to do is configure the profiles you want, and then type: ExtraOutlook.exe &#34;C:\Program Files\Microsoft Office\Office12\OUTLOOK.EXE&#34; (after you download it, of course).&lt;br /&gt;
Attendees of past Microsoft Ninjitsu classes have been using it for some time now (as all attendees get special access to the Hammer of God Member&#39;s Site) and we&#39;ve not heard of any catastrophic failures (you know, like having all mailbox data destroyed without any hope of recovery).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve wanted this for a while now and have bugged it in Office 10 and Office 11.  I have both a personal exchange account and a work exchange account and have not liked having both.  Thusfar, I have coped by using my smartphone for my personal account (as the office does not provide me with cellphone service) and use Outlook for work email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;a href=&#34;http://hammerofgod.com/download.html&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Roundup 2</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/weekend-roundup-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/weekend-roundup-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, I&#39;m a day late, but I have some new links to some interesting software products, a virus warning, and more news:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New Applications:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.odcnms.org/&#34;&gt;Open Data Center Network Management System&lt;/a&gt;&#34; - Late last week, I got an email asking me to evaluate and comment on this new application.  I haven&#39;t had a chance to install or look at it yet, but I wanted to throw it out to everyone until I have time to review it myself.
&lt;p&gt;This appears to be an ideal solution for documenting network data centers, racks, patch panels, routers, etc. - especially for those of us who have to maintain a frugal IT environment (like my office).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This one isn&#39;t new, but I just found it for the first time today.  &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;http://code4ward.net/CS2/Default.aspx&#34;&gt;Royal TS&lt;/a&gt;&#34;.  This is a good replacement for the &#34;Remote Desktops&#34; MMC applet that isn&#39;t available (at least not easily available) on Windows Vista.  It allows you to organize your Remote Desktop sessions in a nice console list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploit / Virus Warning:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This item was more tailored for delivery on Friday, but it doesn&#39;t hurt to reinforce the importance of making sure that your Adobe Acrobat software (either the reader or the creator) is up-to-date.  Last Friday, there was an open exploit using PDF files of the Adobe Acrobat (or Microsoft Windows, if you prefer) flaw that allowed your computer to run exploited code.   I noted two attempts of this virus emailed to my office early morning Saturday morning, but my spam/virus gateway was updated to filter it out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More News:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&#39;m posting in the Microsoft Newsgroups once again (primarily in Vista Networking, Server Networking, DFS, and DNS).  It&#39;s about time that I got back to my &#34;roots&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I had the joy of helping someone install Leopard this weekend.  It seems nice and quick, but I don&#39;t know if I could stand using the Mac OS X user interface long enough to use it.  Also, Parallels was not working properly on the machine I saw, so that would preclude me from using it in an office situation (AutoCAD doesn&#39;t exist in Mac OS X, nor will it ever).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for today.  Have a great week if I don&#39;t post again this week.  I&#39;ll try to be more active than that..  And feel free to send comments.  I&#39;m open to criticism...  :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Roundup 1</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/weekend-roundup-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/weekend-roundup-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the first of (hopefully) a continual series of what is new in the Networking and IT World for the past week:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://channel9.msdn.com/Showpost.aspx?postid=347154&#34;&gt;MS Internal use of Network Access Protection Channel 9 Video&lt;/a&gt; - Jeff Sigman (of the NAP team) and Brent Atkison (of MS-IT) talk about how NAP is implemented on the Microsoft network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://releases.ubuntu.com/7.10/&#34;&gt;Ubuntu 7.10 (GutsyGibbon) &lt;/a&gt;has been released, both in Desktop and Server releases.  For the benefit of others at the office, we have implemented some of our public web servers on Ubuntu (although I am more a Centos or BSD dude...).  Downloads are still rather slow due to the Slashdot effect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weekly Wishlist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; x64 version of PageDefrag for my servers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working version of Veridian on two of my AM2 systems that should support Virtualization, but are disabled due to processor stepping level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Task List for the week:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Installing the RTM build of Windows Home Server at home...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upgrade my Trixbox installation and implement OpenWingo softphones...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Points of Interest</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/points-of-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/points-of-interest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow...  My last post was a holiday ago.  :(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few items of interest:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The wireless WAN problem I mentioned a few months ago has been solved using about $8 of supplies from my local Lowes store.  The problem was due to the extreme heat that we have down here in Central Texas (and to tell you the truth, this has been a pretty cool year).  My solution?  Build a mesh shelter out of storage cubes and patio screen fabric.  My problems are now gone.  Of course, the point would have been made moot in another month or so, but it felt good to get it solved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cisco&#39;s TelePresence room is cool..  If you haven&#39;t seen the TelePresence rooms in one of the local Cisco office, try to make it a point to see it in the future.  This room is like a virtual conference room (which isn&#39;t that special), but there implementation is excellent (with surround sound, similar furniture, etc).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sysprep and Mass Storage Drivers suck.  Actually, that is being too kind.  I spent over a week fighting with Sysprep and getting the 5 different type of Mass Storage devices working on a Windows XP image.  Why Windows XP?  Our LOB applications still do not work reliably under Windows Vista (ESRI, Bentley/Haestad Methods, and Oce Archiving).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More soon..  :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Site Note:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have started locking some of the older posts due to spam problems.  These spam postings never make the public side of the site, but are VERY annoying on the administrative side of the blog.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Breach Notification - A State by State Guide</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/security-breach-notification-a-state-by-state-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/old-network-blog/security-breach-notification-a-state-by-state-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From a mailing list that I am on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;This chart provides information regarding &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.perkinscoie.com/statebreachchart/www.perkinscoie.com/statebreachchart/chart.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;security breach notification&lt;/a&gt; legislation which has been enacted in U.S. jurisdictions. The pioneering statute on this issue, California&#39;s Security Breach Notification Act (Senate Bill No. 1386), is used as the baseline for comparisons herein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.perkinscoie.com/statebreachchart/&#34;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt; (Perkins Coie)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s been out for a while now (March 2007), but somehow I missed it in my security browsing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>