<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accountability Partner on Jeffreys Ruminations</title>
    <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/accountability-partner/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accountability Partner on Jeffreys Ruminations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/accountability-partner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Accountabilibuddy Needed</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Accountabilibuddy-Needed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Accountabilibuddy-Needed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m in need of finding an Accountability Partner for multiple things (one person could satisify both needs).  I need someone to kick my butt to help me keep down on the fitness path - someone who won&amp;rsquo;t take my excuses when I hurt too much or just don&amp;rsquo;t want to do the things that I need to do.  I promise I&amp;rsquo;ll provide the same support to my accountability partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second need is keeping more with the traditional role of the Accountability Partner.  Someone who can keep me following the straight and narrow path.  I have been plagued with thoughts that I should not be thinking.  I have said things that I definitely should not have said.  Like I&amp;rsquo;ve said before, I&amp;rsquo;m a single guy who is still incredibly weak.  The problem I have is that there aren&amp;rsquo;t enough other single guys at church who can satisfy this role for me.  There are married guys, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to reciprocate as an accountability partner with some one who is married because I don&amp;rsquo;t understand or know their perspective of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are in need of an accountability partner, feel free to contact me and we can talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&#34;http://jeffreyrandow.org/accountability-public/&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; for more information on what an Accountability Partner is.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>