<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Longhorn Alumni Band on Jeffreys Ruminations</title>
    <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/longhorn-alumni-band/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Longhorn Alumni Band on Jeffreys Ruminations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/longhorn-alumni-band/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Longhorn Alumni Band 2014</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/longhorn-alumni-band-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/longhorn-alumni-band-2014/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On October 18, 2014, I participated in the 51st Annual Longhorn Alumni Band Reunion at the Texas vs Iowa State.  This was the first time I have participated in the last 10 years (I used to always do it from 1995-2002, but dropped out afterwards).  This completes one item from my Ultimate Quest List for 2014-2015 (see &lt;a href=&#34;http://jeffreyrandow.org/2014/09/28/the-road-ahead-(cnf-part-2)/&#34;&gt;The Road Ahead&lt;/a&gt; for more information on the Ultimate Quest).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this event, I decided to do a couple of videos.  Three of the videos are from me and two are from other people.  I also have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://picasaweb.google.com/105235561941690126130/LonghornAlumniBand2014&#34;&gt;photo gallery&lt;/a&gt; posted at Picasa (and available from the menu above).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also note that the videos were &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; made with a GoPro.  I used my simple camera which does film in HD mode.  This camera was mounted to my tuba with a flexible camera mount.  I was surprised at how stable it was.  Either that, or I remembered how to keep my upper body stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first video is what halftime looks like from my perspective.  I was on the North 15 Yard Line leading a curl from the East sideline.  &lt;strong&gt;Note for those of you who have never experienced marching band, the phasing issues you hear while I am marching is common and due to how sound echoes back in the stadium.  At first, it seems disorienting, but you do get used to it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/ugNnBzQ-9Po&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was funny is that I was not the only person to do this.  A snare drummer also strapped a camera on and video taped halftime.  I say this is funny because we were on the same line and I can see him and his camera from my video and he can see me and my camera from his.  So here is his video for comparison:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/ColoxyOBOrw&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next video was the march from Music Building East to the Stadium including the Ramp Climb from hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/Fsx4X3py7VQ&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next video was my recording of the Longhorn Band Pre-Game show.  Please excuse my &amp;ldquo;sucky&amp;rdquo; singing.  Not used to people actually singing Deep in the Heart of Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/rSWF4OmicKA&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final video is of the entire halftime show taken by someone in the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/I_ZGFUVL4PU&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will I do it again?  Yes.  I had fun.  It was good exercise.  I will try to get more people that I know to go too&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>