<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Psychology on Jeffreys Ruminations</title>
    <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/psychology/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Psychology on Jeffreys Ruminations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/tags/psychology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Living In My World</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/aspergers/living-in-my-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/aspergers/living-in-my-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was browsing reddit like I am prone to do now-a-days and came across a picture that completely captures me in social settings:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-4jktXxEAxM4/TtGkI5x8jTI/AAAAAAAAAK4/_pD0mWiIDeg/s400/cartoon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Me At Parties&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who have been with me at parties - there are typically two ways that I respond.  I show up long enough to be spotted and then quietly and discretely leave without telling anyone, or I blend with the walls and pretty much hide.  This was very evident at one of the wedding showers I attended for Stephen/Danielle&amp;rsquo;s wedding this past March.  Why do I do this?  I&amp;rsquo;m usually completely overwhelmed and my brain shuts down.  Thus I do the two things that will bring me relief.  This is also why I do not allow parties to be thrown on my behalf - It&amp;rsquo;s hard to escape a party when you are the center of attention and I would be so mentally exhausted that it may sometimes make me physically ill.  Before my Asperger&amp;rsquo;s diagnosis, I thought this was entirely social anxiety and shyness - but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t explain the mental exhaustion toll that social interactions may cause me.  But now I understand why I respond in this way and I need to work on how to help solve this problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Small groups are easy (6-8 people).  Technical meetings are OK for me at almost any size.  But social gatherings are very very difficult.  This explains why I tried to hide when I used to attempt to go to my &amp;ldquo;mid-sized&amp;rdquo; small group at church.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you see me like this, you can understand why I&amp;rsquo;m doing this.  It isn&amp;rsquo;t a sign that I&amp;rsquo;m dissing you.  It&amp;rsquo;s just means I must escape to my &amp;ldquo;happy zone&amp;rdquo; from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Credit to &lt;a href=&#34;http://aspiestrategy.blogspot.com/&#34;&gt;Aspie Strategy&lt;/a&gt; blog for the image)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asperger Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/aspergers/aspergers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/aspergers/aspergers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, It has been a while since I have posted.  Many things have taken place since the start of this year, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The start of a new semester at school.  I am taking Data Structures (C+ + ), Discrete Mathematics 2, and Assembly Language (MIPS-32).  I may be on par to finish my certificate by the end of this year, then off to get a MS degree starting next year (while working full-time at that point).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve regressed on my blood clot.  My INR has been down lately for no reason that I can see.  So I&amp;rsquo;m on a frequent testing rotation until it gets stable.  My urological issue remains unsteady, but I feel it will always be undecided on how I&amp;rsquo;m doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week I visited the counseling center at school and took a battery of psychological tests. Apparently I suffer from a form of high functional autism called Asperger&amp;rsquo;s Syndrome.  Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve read the different symptoms of this syndrome, it is very obvious that I meet most of the symptoms and have met them throughout my life (even using the new not-yet-to-be-published DSM-V guidelines).  For most people, this type of diagnosis can be a crushing blow.  In my case, I have had to learn how to accommodate the difference in the way that my brain is wired and have learned  how to interact in a bare-minimum fashion with other people.  As such, the diagnosis was a relief to me in that I now understand many of the weird idiosyncrasies that I shared with no one else that I knew.For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know what the base symptoms of Asperger&amp;rsquo;s Syndrome, it can be basically broken down to having several of the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limited empathy towards others (It&amp;rsquo;s not that I don&amp;rsquo;t have empathy, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen automatically)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsteady gait, balance, coordination issues&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lack of noticing verbal and non-verbal clues from others&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communications difficulties with other (i.e., due to taking most concepts literally, not being able to look at people in the eyes, not picking up social cues in conversations, etc)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intense interest in certain topics, especially those dealing with math, science, engineering, and technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Detail oriented - Finding details/patterns or arriving at especially unique solutions to problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late Speech Development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dislike physical contact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extremely good long term memory, terrible short term memory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Difficulty in reading emotions in others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many more symptoms, but these are the key ones in my diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many online quizzes out there that can give you a quick analysis, but still you need a professional analysis to be sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, my score on the most comprehensive of the tests is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Aspie score: 170 of 200&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your neurotypical (non-autistic) score: 25 of 200&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are very likely an Aspie&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://rdos.net/eng/Aspie-quiz.php&#34;&gt;Aspie Quiz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.jeffreyrandow.org/images/asperger.png&#34; alt=&#34;My Asperger Chart&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess that is it for now.  I have two concerts that I need to process and post, but that will be next weekend at the earliest.  Have a great week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life at a Crossroads - The Brick Wall</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/life-at-a-crossroads-the-brick-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/life-at-a-crossroads-the-brick-wall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As some of you may know, I have been battling many demons this year – some health-related, some work-related, and many personal struggles.  Throughout these trials and tribulations, I have acquired a few new insights into myself and have noticed the gaping chasm that I am either unable or (shudder) unwilling to cross in all areas of my life.  To put it in the parlance of the Easter sermon from church this weekend – I have hit my brick wall.  This brick wall is of my own creation and somehow I must break through it if I am to progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is this wall?  The bricks of it are worry, anxiety, indecisiveness, and pessimism.  How do I manifest this?  The biggest brick is that of worry.  I worry much less now than I did in the past, but still it is a major part of my life.  Most of my decisions are made to minimize worry (or change) – many to the detriment of what I need to do.  Combine this worry and my natural sense of pessimism fuels one of my major problems – hypochondriaism.   I am guessing that much of the pain that I have felt in the past two or three months have been fueled by this sense of worry and pessimism (and a dose of stress, to be sure).  It is this pessimism that leads me to think the worst of any possible situation.  Even now, I have been thinking of the worst case scenario from my last procedure and have been planning on what I should do now – before I have any clue of how it went.  This leads to a downward spiral that never seems to end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Worry, anxiety, and indecisiveness fuel another of my life’s battles – that of work.  I’ll be honest and say that I dislike work.  I like most of the people and some of the things that I do, but in general, work has been more drudgery than a positive experience.  Worry and anxiety play a big role in this matter – worry in that I fear the unknown and anxiety in that I won’t be able to fit in or have enough knowledge in whatever new endeavors I may follow.  My current job has been my first “real” job (by “real”, I’m discounting jobs that I had either in or before college) and fear not having the safety or security of a job has kept me chained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But now back to this wall that interferes with so much of life.    There is a root solution to this, and it is one that I find incredibly difficult.  It is a matter of “faith”.  It is clear that my worry and anxiety is fueled by my limited faith (Matthew 8:26 – “You of little faith, why are you so afraid?”).  I have had this confirmed in a discussion a few months ago with a friend who told me that I was probably the strongest Christian he knew who had so little faith.  That comment stung then and now, but it is true.  This is a prime area that I need to focus on – by letting go and having faith.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the Easter sermon I attended yesterday, one of the things we were to do is to fill out a card describing our own personal “brick wall” and that the pastor would pray to help us overcome this obstacle.  Any guesses on what my card mentioned?  Helping me to extend my faith and learn to let go and give my life completely to God.  With more faith, my struggles with worry (Matthew 6:27-29 “Can any one of you by worrying add a single hour to your life?  And why do you worry about clothes? See how the flowers of the field grow. They do not labor or spin. Yet I tell you that not even Solomon in all his splendor was dressed like one of these.  If that is how God clothes the grass of the field, which is here today and tomorrow is thrown into the fire, will he not much more clothe you—you of little faith?” or 1 Peter 5:7 – “Give all your worries and cares to God, for he cares about you.”), anxiety (Phillipians 4:6-7 – “Do not be anxious about anything, but in everything, by prayer and petition, with thanksgiving, present your requests to God. And the peace of God, which transcends all understanding, will guard your hearts and your minds in Christ Jesus”), or pessimism (Matthew 19:26 – “With God, all things are possible.”) should be overcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of my struggles with faith has been discerning what I should do.  I have asked for guidance, but my ears aren’t attuned to hear the words of the Lord.  I have only heard the words of the Lord in times of extreme stress in my life and I have heeded the guidance.  I pray for guidance, but I’m oblivious to many of the cues.  Others have told me they see the direction I am to go, but I am still blind and deaf.  This is an area of my life that I must tackle and attune my ears and heart toward God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pray for me.  Pray that my faith is strengthened and that I learn to be attuned towards the will of God.  Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/september-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/september-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just posted what was probably my first three page long rant posting.  It&amp;rsquo;s password protected as it was only meant for me to have a relief posting.  It helped somewhat&amp;hellip;  :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On to my regular posting.  It has been almost five months since the incident.  I&amp;rsquo;m still struggling with raw emotions, grief, and regrets quite a few times a week.  It&amp;rsquo;s getting better in some ways and worse in other ways.  This is normal, though.  Time will act as the best salve for what is vexing me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;rsquo;t comment on work other than to say that I am not a happy camper right now&amp;hellip;  Four of my officemates, though, have been of incredible help and comfort to me as of late.  I will try to be a better and happier worker, but it will require a strength of will and forgiveness that will be difficult for me to muster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since my last posting, I have gone to two high school football games (New Braunfels versus Seguin and NB Canyon), one college game (UT vs FAU), and a game watching party for the UT vs UTEP game last night.  I used to go to the high school football games all the time back when my father was still alive, so going back proved to be a good distraction for me.  So good, in fact, that I ended up buying season tickets for New Braunfels home games.  The UT/FAU game was my normal opening game that I have attended every year since 1997 when I first started getting UT season tickets.  And last night, a college friend who lives in New Braunfels decided to hold a game watching party at his house.  He projected the game against a sheet hung over his (open) garage door.  The weather was perfect and the fellowship was great.  As for church, I spent the past two weeks at Oakwood Baptist in New Braunfels - last week at their Sunday night service and then I was invited to one of the morning services this morning.  I like their church - I just wish it had more traditional worship.  I prefer the Sunday evening as it is in a much smaller and cozier venue and I don&amp;rsquo;t have to fight parking to get in and out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week I have two more games and I will be staying up in Austin to geocache after the game - that or climbing Mt Bonnell.  I have a Doctor appointment on Friday that I am a bit concerned about (the pinched nerve, or what I think is a pinched nerve, in my toe is a bit concerning) and Rudy has a vet visit Friday afternoon for his last set of puppy shots.  And this weekend, I think I will check out Crossroads Community Church in Austin - another college friend is on the staff their and listening to a few of the sermons online proves that they are orthodox which is a requirement for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That will be it for now.  Thanks for listening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YBIC, Jeffrey&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August Musings</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/august-musings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/august-musings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, we have finally reached August, temperatures are hitting record highs, and summer is finally close to being over.  This year has been bad.  Much of it has to do with the events of March and April, but sometimes life is zigging when I want it to zag. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This weekend posed new problems - of which I don&amp;rsquo;t need more of.  On top of everything I must deal with on the house and the property, I now &amp;ldquo;function&amp;rdquo; as a home for a family of skunks.  I ended up trapping five of them yesterday and I have at least two left to trap.  Fortunately, Rudy (my puppy) finally could get his rabies shot last Friday, but the fact that skunks are so close makes me nervous.  Alas, the two remaining skunks apparently are smarter than the five I trapped yesterday since they have avoided the cage like the plague.  Hopefully they will be trapped tomorrow and I can feel safe leaving Rudy outside when I&amp;rsquo;m not around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This same weekend also saw me miss my continuing education opportunity up in Austin, get stuck behind an accident on IH 35 north of Buda that shut the interstate down for hours (I didn&amp;rsquo;t wait - I got off the highway and followed the back roads to get to Austin).  Installing a motion light took hours when it should have only taken a few minutes.  You get the point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week also is (hopefully) my last stressful week at work.  We have been working on DFIRM protests and appeals for the past ninety days.  The deadline for these appeals/protests/etc are due at the close of business on Wednesday.  So the next three days are going to suck, but I will be taking off Thursday and now that we are on ten hour days (starting tomorrow), we will have Friday(s) off.  Now I just will need to wait out the next round of comings and goings at the office.  The housing bubble has now hit San Antonio with a vengeance.  Not like the 80&amp;rsquo;s or California today, but still very bad.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been expecting this the past two years as I like to keep track of real estate for possible future investment opportunities, but we haven&amp;rsquo;t hit the bottom and we won&amp;rsquo;t hit the bottom yet due to the mortgage bailout. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enough depressing talk, though this isn&amp;rsquo;t much better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, when I went to church (went to an evening service due to the skunk problem above), I picked up one of the Celebrate Recovery - Codependency brochure.  This seems very much like what is definately wrong with me:  Assume responsibility for others;  Guilt; Difficulty expressing feelings; afraid of being hurt/rejected by others; minimize/deny how you feel; put others (opinions, feelings, needs, or desires) before your own; judge everything harshly;etc&amp;hellip;  I did realize this was a problem - I know I was codependent with my mother.  However most literature about codependency refers to some sort of abuse - chemical, physical, etc.  This wasn&amp;rsquo;t my situation.  So I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to use the common reference materials to fight codependency.  Even now, I still am wandering around aimlessly trying to find a new target to attach myself to.  This is dangerous and disasterous for me.  I know I must overcome.  Aarrgghh..  Why can&amp;rsquo;t life be simpler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On that same vein, I need to learn how to make relationships.  I&amp;rsquo;m afraid to do so.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been afraid for most of my life.  The few that I have had have been wonderful, but not made to last.  I know that I am still in the beginning of the grieving process.  This will limit me to some point and I need to be careful of what relationships I do make as I would be more &amp;ldquo;vulnerable&amp;rdquo; than I would otherwise be.  However, loneliness and depression will follow if I don&amp;rsquo;t tackle this problem.  I want to live in a comfort zone.  I mustn&amp;rsquo;t do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, enough for this post for now.  I&amp;rsquo;ll post back letter and make sure you keep me in your prayers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Jeffrey&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>