<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Jeffreys Ruminations</title>
    <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/categories/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Jeffreys Ruminations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Update - Summer 2016</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/temp-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/temp-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have not forgotten about the blog.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with school and work, and also am attempting to move the blog from Jekyll to either Pelican (Python) or Hugo (Go).  I&amp;rsquo;m much more familiar with those languages than I am with Ruby (Jekyll).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also had to make an update to move my audio and graphical assets away from google storage to Amazon S3.  My audio may get moved again if the download of the files will cause a great increase in cost.  I&amp;rsquo;ll update soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Longhorn Alumni Band 2014</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/longhorn-alumni-band-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/longhorn-alumni-band-2014/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On October 18, 2014, I participated in the 51st Annual Longhorn Alumni Band Reunion at the Texas vs Iowa State.  This was the first time I have participated in the last 10 years (I used to always do it from 1995-2002, but dropped out afterwards).  This completes one item from my Ultimate Quest List for 2014-2015 (see &lt;a href=&#34;http://jeffreyrandow.org/2014/09/28/the-road-ahead-(cnf-part-2)/&#34;&gt;The Road Ahead&lt;/a&gt; for more information on the Ultimate Quest).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this event, I decided to do a couple of videos.  Three of the videos are from me and two are from other people.  I also have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://picasaweb.google.com/105235561941690126130/LonghornAlumniBand2014&#34;&gt;photo gallery&lt;/a&gt; posted at Picasa (and available from the menu above).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also note that the videos were &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; made with a GoPro.  I used my simple camera which does film in HD mode.  This camera was mounted to my tuba with a flexible camera mount.  I was surprised at how stable it was.  Either that, or I remembered how to keep my upper body stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first video is what halftime looks like from my perspective.  I was on the North 15 Yard Line leading a curl from the East sideline.  &lt;strong&gt;Note for those of you who have never experienced marching band, the phasing issues you hear while I am marching is common and due to how sound echoes back in the stadium.  At first, it seems disorienting, but you do get used to it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/ugNnBzQ-9Po&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was funny is that I was not the only person to do this.  A snare drummer also strapped a camera on and video taped halftime.  I say this is funny because we were on the same line and I can see him and his camera from my video and he can see me and my camera from his.  So here is his video for comparison:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/ColoxyOBOrw&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next video was the march from Music Building East to the Stadium including the Ramp Climb from hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/Fsx4X3py7VQ&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next video was my recording of the Longhorn Band Pre-Game show.  Please excuse my &amp;ldquo;sucky&amp;rdquo; singing.  Not used to people actually singing Deep in the Heart of Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/rSWF4OmicKA&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final video is of the entire halftime show taken by someone in the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe
  width=&#34;560&#34;
  height=&#34;315&#34;
  src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/I_ZGFUVL4PU&#34;
  frameborder=&#34;0&#34;
  allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will I do it again?  Yes.  I had fun.  It was good exercise.  I will try to get more people that I know to go too&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tag Support</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Tag-Support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Tag-Support/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The theme now supports tags, tag pages, and a tag cloud.  This functionality requires you to run a utility before pushing your updates to Github Pages.  In order to use tags, you need to add the following information into your YAML front matter:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;{% highlight yaml linenos %}
tags:
    - Tag Name (can be multiple words)
{% endhighlight %}&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tag pages will be stored in the /tags directory and the tagcloud.html file (include wherever you want to use it) is saved in the _includes directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To create the tag pages and tag cloud, you will need to use the new Rakefile support (see below).  Running &lt;code&gt;rake deploy&lt;/code&gt; will automatically create the tag pages before committing the changes and pushing to github.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, tags support the banner functionality as described.  If either the &lt;code&gt;banner&lt;/code&gt; id or the &lt;code&gt;bannertitle&lt;/code&gt; name match the tag name, then that banner will be incorporated on that tag page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;rakefile-support&#34;&gt;Rakefile support:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website supports the following rake commands:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake post[&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;]&lt;/code&gt; - Creates a post with the title &amp;ldquo;title&amp;rdquo; and saved into the _posts directory with the current date.  It will then open up your text editor (specified in config.yml).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake draft[&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;]&lt;/code&gt; - Similar to post, but this will make it a draft without the post date and will not publish it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake publish&lt;/code&gt; - Promote a draft posting to a real posting.  It will move the file from the _drafts directory to the _posts directory and will change the post date to the current date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake page[&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;]&lt;/code&gt; - Like posts, but this time with a page.  It is moved to the pages folder by default.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake build&lt;/code&gt; - This will build the tag pages and will also build the full site, but &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; serve it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake watch&lt;/code&gt; - Builds the site and tags, then serve it.  It will also regenerate on post/page/draft changes.  You can also run &lt;code&gt;rake watch[&amp;quot;drafts&amp;quot;]&lt;/code&gt; which will also preview the draft postings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake preview&lt;/code&gt; - This will build the site/tags, then open up a web browser to preview the website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake deploy[&amp;quot;Message&amp;quot;]&lt;/code&gt; - This will build the tag pages, add new files to the local git repository, commit the changes with the message &amp;ldquo;Message&amp;rdquo;, then push the local git repository to your origin master (likely to be github)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;rake tags&lt;/code&gt; - This will just build the tag pages and tag cloud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to do the post/page publishing, there are two prototype files in the root directory that are named &lt;code&gt;_post.txt&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;_page.txt&lt;/code&gt; (these names can be updated by changing some variables in the _config.yml file).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;5-27-14&#34;&gt;5/27/14&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Added an &lt;a href=&#34;https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/archives/&#34;&gt;Archives&lt;/a&gt; Page.  It still kinda sucks, but I&amp;rsquo;ll work on it..  Look under the category menu.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Updates and Musings</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Life-Updates-And-Musings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Life-Updates-And-Musings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(includes updates from May 25, 2014 - JER)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten this website to a functional level, so I guess it is time to do an update on what is going on in my life right now.  It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy time, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been enjoying myself working on some interesting projects at work.  Life is different in the non-engineering world and I think it would have been better if I had changed a few years earlier than I did.  I do some programming, but I am starting to get a bit rusty due to a lack of practice.  Most of the programming that I have been doing has been Python scripting, with a bit of web programming mixed in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took the spring semester off of school in order to work on all of the special projects at work that hopefully will be done by the end of summer.  I then plan on restarting school in some form or fashion either in the fall or next spring.  I have been asked in the past about why I&amp;rsquo;m actually going to school.  The answer is mainly to help me keep my sanity and to maintain at least a modicum of social life.  In the past, I would just hibernate in my house after work and never get out and do things.  This is not healthy for me.  School (at least at Texas State) requires me to interact with other people and I actually had some sort of social life while going to school.  UTSA has been a bit different in that regards, however.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may be seeing more postings of me on Facebook or Twitter about my new fitness kick.  About two months ago I was diagnosed with Type II diabetes.  I thought that my kicking of the soft drink habit would help keep my sugar levels down, but apparently my substitute drink was worse (sweet tea, then half-and-half tea).  So I started taking Lantus at the end of March.  This has lowered my blood sugars considerably.  However, I do not plan on staying on the regimen for a long period of time.  In order for that to happen, I must lose a lot of weight.  So I&amp;rsquo;m walking/jogging several times a week and have changed my diet to a more &amp;ldquo;Paleo&amp;rdquo; form.  I post a daily log of what I&amp;rsquo;m doing on Twitter under the username &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jeffreyfitness&#34;&gt;@jeffreyfitness&lt;/a&gt;.  These include the tracks from MapMyRun and a weight/blood sugar log.  I&amp;rsquo;m using this feed as my accountability log.  I&amp;rsquo;m also following the suggestions from the Nerd Fitness website for starting a bit of strength training and just fitness in general.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have started to do my workouts (other than the walking/jogging) at either Planet Fitness in New Braunfels (for a lack of a better place to go that has hours that I can live with) and the LA Fitness on 410/Blanco in San Antonio (it is close to work, fairly cheap, and has a pool that I can start doing AquaFit).  I&amp;rsquo;m curious about the ResoluteFit option at the new hospital in New Braunfels, but they have not posted much information other than telling you to email their staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What else is going on?  I&amp;rsquo;m living with my ongoing battle with my house.  I think I have figured out that I&amp;rsquo;m not going to rebuild it, but I will need to hire a remodeling person/company to fix my ceilings (remove the popcorn that hasn&amp;rsquo;t already fallen and fix all my corners by retaping) and to do something about my dysfunctional bathroom(s) and kitchen.  I think I have a wall of mold behind my shower and I do not have a working lavatory sink in my master bathroom.  I don&amp;rsquo;t want anything special or high end for any of these rooms.  The house is not being improved for resell value - it needs to be improved to make it more functional and usable.  I&amp;rsquo;m also starting to get rid of more things.  Anyone want some China?  I&amp;rsquo;m a guy and I don&amp;rsquo;t ever see me having any dinner parties at my house which would require China.  Besides, it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been used in over 20 years.  I truly don&amp;rsquo;t even see the point of having a dining room.  I pretty much just set stuff down on the table and leave it there.  I have a small table in the kitchen that I use for meals and the such.  It doesn&amp;rsquo;t fit very well, though.  The kitchen could be reconfigured to some point.  I just have no clue where to begin or whom to call to even talk about this.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky:  Site Status Report</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Status-Report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Status-Report/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This will be a &lt;em&gt;sticky&lt;/em&gt; post that I will update as I change things on the site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of May 12, 2014, I have finished the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Imported all of the old postings from Wordpress and migrated them to the new system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implemented Blog Roll.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got MediaElements.JS to finally cooperate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photo Galleries online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set up GDrive CDN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work to be done:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish Templating (Author)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter Card&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open Graph&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collections&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This has been a fun project.  It has taught me a lot about HTML 5 and made me appreciate Ruby to at least a small extent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;may-18-2014-update&#34;&gt;May 18, 2014 Update&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did a little cleanup on the site and have started to implement banners on certain post types (See any of the music postings).  I still need to tweak it some, though.  I haven&amp;rsquo;t spent any time on the site the last week except for this morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;june-15-2014-update&#34;&gt;June 15, 2014 Update&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a catchup post.  The site now supports Tags and Archive pages &lt;a href=&#34;http://jeffreyrandow.org/2014/05/30/Tag-Support/&#34;&gt;(See this Post)&lt;/a&gt;.  This means that I  can&amp;rsquo;t completely run this on Github Pages, but it is very easy to implement and still use Github Pages.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll Site Launch</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Jekyll-Site-Relaunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/Jekyll-Site-Relaunch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am currently in the process of relaunching my personal blog from Wordpress to a
static publishing engine named &amp;ldquo;Jekyll&amp;rdquo;.  This entails a major design shift and I
am rearchitecting my data to be cloud hosted (using Google Drive as a CDN - Content
Delivery Network - for my concert MP3&amp;rsquo;s and other larger/hosted files) with the
base site running on Github Pages (though I could also host it on Amazon S3,
Rackspace Cloud, or even CloudFlare).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why am I doing this?  Wordpress rocks as a website engine and I&amp;rsquo;m currently using it
to do a web page re-write for my office.  But for my personal needs, it is way too
bloated and overkill for what I need.  Plus I can now pretty much leave the site
and not worry about security (since it is all static html).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why Jekyll?  At first, I was planning on using Pelican, but it is extremely inflexible
about using your custom URLs.  Yes, I know you can force it, but it was not very elegant.
Besides, I also just wanted to host the file and not have to worry about building it
myself.  Why not Ghost?  See my reasonings for Wordpress above, and I dislike using
Javascript as a language (Ghost uses Node.JS) and would like to see it&amp;rsquo;s early demise.
(Yeah, I know, I&amp;rsquo;m using plenty of Javascript on this site, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that
I have to like it).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What should you get?  Faster loading.  A more cohesive appearance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do I get?  A chance to code.  I primarily use Python and shell/Powershell scripting
now-a-days and need to keep up my code chops.  Plus, at this rate, I&amp;rsquo;ll have Ruby
down pat soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d like to make a shout out to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jordanthornquest.com&#34;&gt;Jordan Thornquest&lt;/a&gt; who provided
me with the base theme that I have forked and added on to.  I still have lots to do to
bring the site completely back onine (I&amp;rsquo;m going to add banner pictures, make more
category pages, and stuff like that), but I have to correct all of the old content
migrated over from Wordpress.  I have half a mind to convert most of it over to
Markdown from HTML, but that will be on a time available basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anywho, that is enough for now.  More work tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life at a Crossroads - The Brick Wall</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/life-at-a-crossroads-the-brick-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/life-at-a-crossroads-the-brick-wall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As some of you may know, I have been battling many demons this year – some health-related, some work-related, and many personal struggles.  Throughout these trials and tribulations, I have acquired a few new insights into myself and have noticed the gaping chasm that I am either unable or (shudder) unwilling to cross in all areas of my life.  To put it in the parlance of the Easter sermon from church this weekend – I have hit my brick wall.  This brick wall is of my own creation and somehow I must break through it if I am to progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is this wall?  The bricks of it are worry, anxiety, indecisiveness, and pessimism.  How do I manifest this?  The biggest brick is that of worry.  I worry much less now than I did in the past, but still it is a major part of my life.  Most of my decisions are made to minimize worry (or change) – many to the detriment of what I need to do.  Combine this worry and my natural sense of pessimism fuels one of my major problems – hypochondriaism.   I am guessing that much of the pain that I have felt in the past two or three months have been fueled by this sense of worry and pessimism (and a dose of stress, to be sure).  It is this pessimism that leads me to think the worst of any possible situation.  Even now, I have been thinking of the worst case scenario from my last procedure and have been planning on what I should do now – before I have any clue of how it went.  This leads to a downward spiral that never seems to end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Worry, anxiety, and indecisiveness fuel another of my life’s battles – that of work.  I’ll be honest and say that I dislike work.  I like most of the people and some of the things that I do, but in general, work has been more drudgery than a positive experience.  Worry and anxiety play a big role in this matter – worry in that I fear the unknown and anxiety in that I won’t be able to fit in or have enough knowledge in whatever new endeavors I may follow.  My current job has been my first “real” job (by “real”, I’m discounting jobs that I had either in or before college) and fear not having the safety or security of a job has kept me chained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But now back to this wall that interferes with so much of life.    There is a root solution to this, and it is one that I find incredibly difficult.  It is a matter of “faith”.  It is clear that my worry and anxiety is fueled by my limited faith (Matthew 8:26 – “You of little faith, why are you so afraid?”).  I have had this confirmed in a discussion a few months ago with a friend who told me that I was probably the strongest Christian he knew who had so little faith.  That comment stung then and now, but it is true.  This is a prime area that I need to focus on – by letting go and having faith.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the Easter sermon I attended yesterday, one of the things we were to do is to fill out a card describing our own personal “brick wall” and that the pastor would pray to help us overcome this obstacle.  Any guesses on what my card mentioned?  Helping me to extend my faith and learn to let go and give my life completely to God.  With more faith, my struggles with worry (Matthew 6:27-29 “Can any one of you by worrying add a single hour to your life?  And why do you worry about clothes? See how the flowers of the field grow. They do not labor or spin. Yet I tell you that not even Solomon in all his splendor was dressed like one of these.  If that is how God clothes the grass of the field, which is here today and tomorrow is thrown into the fire, will he not much more clothe you—you of little faith?” or 1 Peter 5:7 – “Give all your worries and cares to God, for he cares about you.”), anxiety (Phillipians 4:6-7 – “Do not be anxious about anything, but in everything, by prayer and petition, with thanksgiving, present your requests to God. And the peace of God, which transcends all understanding, will guard your hearts and your minds in Christ Jesus”), or pessimism (Matthew 19:26 – “With God, all things are possible.”) should be overcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of my struggles with faith has been discerning what I should do.  I have asked for guidance, but my ears aren’t attuned to hear the words of the Lord.  I have only heard the words of the Lord in times of extreme stress in my life and I have heeded the guidance.  I pray for guidance, but I’m oblivious to many of the cues.  Others have told me they see the direction I am to go, but I am still blind and deaf.  This is an area of my life that I must tackle and attune my ears and heart toward God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pray for me.  Pray that my faith is strengthened and that I learn to be attuned towards the will of God.  Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadie</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/roadie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/roadie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, maybe not quite&amp;hellip;  I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning a lot of the background of sound engineering from the friends at church.  It is a much different world than what I am used to and I can definately say that it is fun.  :)  (Fun isn&amp;rsquo;t a word you normally hear out of my mouth).  It can be work, especially with transporting the equipment and the teardown, but it is a good labor of love.  Especially when it is for a good cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link of the Week:  &lt;a href=&#34;http://stagecraft.theprices.net/gallery/cablewrap/cablewrap-qt.html&#34;&gt;Stagelight - How to Do Cable Wrapping&lt;/a&gt; - I learned this one from Philip, Jeff, and Doug last night, but the video helps to reinforce the idea.  This will show you how to wind cables in such a way that you could hold one end and throw the rest of it to unwind it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post is also my attempt to renew my blogging.  This blog is strictly for my personal and non-computer-techy thoughts.  I haven&amp;rsquo;t been the most active person the past few weeks/months/years.  I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that this will act as a part of my re-engaging my passions of life that I have been either purposefully or unconsciously been ignoring to my detriment.  I feel like I am so behind in what I could and should be doing.  It&amp;rsquo;s time to stop being so regimented in things that must get done.  I&amp;rsquo;m living in a such a world that I will be (and have been) buried by the self-imposed obligations that are of little importance in the long term.  (And no, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I am ready to quit just yet&amp;hellip;  Sorry&amp;hellip;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More later as I try to follow this latest path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. My Network Blog should get a bit more active, but I have been so out of it lately that I don&amp;rsquo;t feel qualified to post anything there&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Hermine Redux</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/tropical-storm-hermine-redux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/tropical-storm-hermine-redux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My official total as of 8 AM Wednesday morning is 6.89 inches of total rainfall.  We are expecting more this afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt of an email I sent to my office staff:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the (immediate) aftermath of Tropical Storm Hermine, I thought you might like to know the total precipitation that has fallen as a result of this storm.  This data was obtained by individuals using high accuracy manual rain gauges and are part of the CoCoRaHS network (Community Collaborative Rain, Hail, and Snow Network) – I’m station TX-CML-38.  The graphs below indicate the total precipitation recorded in the prior 24 hour period.  For the purpose of determining the total rainfall, add up the two values from both maps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional data like this is available at &lt;a href=&#34;http://cocorahs.org/Maps/ViewMap.aspx&#34;&gt;http://cocorahs.org/Maps/ViewMap.aspx&lt;/a&gt; for different counties and different days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total Precipitation for Bexar County as of 7 AM Wednesday, September 8, 2010&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.jeffreyrandow.org/images/ts1.png&#34; alt=&#34;September 8 2010&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total Precipitation for Bexar County as of 7 AM Tuesday, September 7, 2010&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s3.amazonaws.com/static.jeffreyrandow.org/images/ts2.png&#34; alt=&#34;September 9 2010&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Las Vegas Trip Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/las-vegas-trip-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/las-vegas-trip-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am now back home from my weekend trip to Las Vegas to celebrate Tommy&amp;rsquo;s upcoming wedding. We left at dark oclock on Thursday morning and arrived home late Saturday night. A total of eleven people went including some fellow co-workers and even my overall boss. As some of you may know, I had decided after my 2003 Las Vegas trip vowing never to return. It would take a lot of convincing or a special event to get me to reconsider going. So in the end, I finally relented and agreed to attend towards the end of April. My reasons for going back are varied and many, but I will address some of them below. Before continuing, I want to assure my fellow sojourners from the trip that I will abide by the &amp;ldquo;What Happens In Vegas Stays In Vegas&amp;rdquo; saying. I have posted a few photos here (and will be adding more once I unpack my camera) of both the sights (and in some cases, sounds) and people of Las Vegas. Now as for my thoughts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travelling with other people is much more fun..  This is probably one of the things that got me started on the wrong foot with Las Vegas in my 2003 trip.  When I went last time, I was with people that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t met before in person (we all got to know each other pretty well as time went on), but we were still total strangers with each other.  This time, I went with four coworkers, one ex-coworker, one person I knew fairly well, two people I&amp;rsquo;ve met before but didn&amp;rsquo;t know too well, and two other new people.  There is comfort when traveling with people you know.  Thus I was more apt to be open and trying to broaden my horizons.  In the end, I got to know three of my non-coworkers much better and was at ease in talking and interacting with all (that&amp;rsquo;s a new one for me in two days).  I&amp;rsquo;m always up to travel and would be overjoyed to travel with anyone that I know (and if I can get off of work, but I have plenty of time off to use).  Travelling alone sucks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I started my trip more on the depressed side (not due to the trip, but I&amp;rsquo;m just describing my general state of mind pre-trip), but I leave with hope.  Hope for relationships.  Hope for what could be.  Hope for changes.  Optimism is not something that I have an abundance of.  This is something I could have accomplished anywhere, but Las Vegas is like an alien nation compared to the comfort and familiarity of Texas.  I had experiences and saw things that showed me that anything is possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of the things others can tell you about me and this trip is that I was more open to getting out of my comfort zone.  I still wasn&amp;rsquo;t as open as I could have been, but then I went a bit more open that what I had planned to in the first place.  Again, this openness is caused by me feeling a sense of comfort and safety that point number one provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I did generally enjoy myself.  I regret not taking the time getting to the swimming pool or staying up later like some of the others were able to do.  But it was as much a learning environment for me as it was entertainment/vacation.  If you were one of my sojourners, I took at least one (but probably much more) nugget of wisdom away from our interactions.  Thank you for that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This one seems out of place, but I do feel like I&amp;rsquo;m getting in better shape..  I walked all over the strip each day (even in the Las Vegas heat).  I did the equivalent of the Tropicana to Bellagio Loop (about 3 miles round trip) multiple times each day and didn&amp;rsquo;t struggle at all.  That is something major for me..  Plus I was easy in comfort on the airplanes (although the last flight did have a mighty short seat belt, but I still fit it).  So I no longer need to fear flying.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone seemed to enjoy the trip.  Some people had better gambling experiences than others (I ended up $45 dollars, but I also hardly spent anything - I love the electronic lady blackjack machine at Binions).  A lot of great food (I love Brazilian Steakhouses - Texas de Brazil and others liked Emeril). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The bad thing about the trip was how expensive everything seemed.  Las Vegas needs to solve the traffic gridlock problems.  I was able to walk from the Tropicana to the Bellagio while making a quick stop in Walgreens for a water in the same amount as a cab took on the same journey.  That is unreal.   The traffic makes all cab rides at least eight to ten dollars and an average of 20 dollars.  Also the city should consider extending the monrail to the downtown area (i.e., Fremont Street).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yes, that is the answer to my question about whether I enjoyed the experience.  Will I go back?  If someone else will come with me, yes.  But then let me say I am willing to travel and do anything that is physically possible for me (so no mountain climbing YET) and with enough notice to be able to get off.  I&amp;rsquo;m even willing to try new things (would I have gone to a Brazilian steakhouse by myself?  not on your life&amp;hellip;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More individual stories later as I will be VERY BUSY the next two days to make up for being gone the end of last week&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, thank you my fellow sojourners for an awesome experience&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Year Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/first-year-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/first-year-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It has now been one full year since I had to &amp;ldquo;press the reset button of life&amp;rdquo;. I can&amp;rsquo;t say that the past year has been easy. It has been rough. Terribly rough. But it is a phase of my life that I must push through, regardless if I want to or not.   I&amp;rsquo;m writing this posting to talk about things that I have learned over the past year and some of the areas that I need to improve on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things that I have learned:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That it is possible to make changes even when everything seems so bleak, so hopeless.  Change was necessary to keep from drowning in pain and suffering.  Change is not easy.  There were times that I practically hated myself for making the same &amp;ldquo;destructive&amp;rdquo; decisions because they were too comfortable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have learned that everyone has a purpose.  One person can impact a countless number of lives.  I think back to the number of people who I had influenced over the year and I was staggered by the implications.  Friends, family, enemies, and even people whom I have never met were impacted by my existence.  This thought alone, as strange as it may seem, helped me on the path of &amp;ldquo;coping&amp;rdquo; (I can&amp;rsquo;t say recover because I haven&amp;rsquo;t recovered and won&amp;rsquo;t do so for some time).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life can and will be cruel.  I learned this lesson the hard way.  It&amp;rsquo;s not something that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know beforehand, but I &amp;ldquo;noticed&amp;rdquo; it more afterwards.  However, these experiences strengthen us and can positively impact our life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relationships in life are important.  Too bad that I completely suck at making and maintaining them.  This is the aspect I need to improve on the most, but one that is dependent on solving other issues of my life first (i.e., self worth).  Also, I need to mention that there have been some very important people in my life the past year who have helped me survive the &amp;ldquo;storms of my life&amp;rdquo; over the past year and I sincerely thank them for their help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things that I need to improve on:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From above, I mentioned &amp;ldquo;self worth&amp;rdquo;.  I&amp;rsquo;m getting better at having a more positive &amp;ldquo;self esteem&amp;rdquo;, but I&amp;rsquo;m not quite there yet.  As I also mentioned, this is hurting me in other aspects of my life.  I need to work on this, but this requires a fundamental change of my personality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get out more.  I still stress on the &amp;ldquo;getting things done&amp;rdquo; phase of life and haven&amp;rsquo;t learned to relax yet.  Again, this requires a change in my personality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I need to get a sense of humor.  I&amp;rsquo;m very serious, normally.  If you know me well, you know that it is possible that I can have humor in my life.  But generally that side of me is very reserved.  I&amp;rsquo;m normally very serious.  I&amp;rsquo;m not a cut-up.  I don&amp;rsquo;t seek attention (actually, I tend to run whenever a spotlight is on me).  It&amp;rsquo;s this level of discomfort I must resolve.  Again, this is (partially) related to the first required improvement above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are still times in my life when I wonder to myself - Why?  What&amp;rsquo;s the purpose?.  These times are scary.  I&amp;rsquo;m happy to say that they come less frequently over the past few months.  Grief sucks.  It is, however, a necessary phase of life that everyone must go through.  And it can be a slow harrowing process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-more information later-&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Showers</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/april-showers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/april-showers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s about time for me to post an update and brain dump:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The planter garden is done (for now) with four rosebushes (three of which are blooming right now), six marigolds, 5 daylilies, and a few cannas.  I still have much more to plant, but I want to make sure that these things live first.  I have seven tomato plants with three actual tomatoes on them (and many, many blooms) and more onions than what I know what do with (I love onions).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I put in a floor with carpet tiles in the spare bedroom and started moving things in there.  This a relief as that room was just a junk repository for years.  I still haven&amp;rsquo;t moved the bed in, but that will happen by next weekend.  So if any of y&amp;rsquo;all out there want to come to New Braunfels to tube or go to Wurstfest and need a place to crash, you know where to call.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m working on my home office/workout room.  This is very much a work in progress.  I think I have finally picked out a paint color to use.  My next task is to move the bed into the spare bedroom, then to paint.  I should be done with desks since I went to IKEA this past weekend to pick up a new table and office stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Spring Concert for the Comal Community Band was today.  A good time was had by all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I went and spent a weekend at Rockport the last week of March.  This was my first trip there in 11 years since my dad passed away.  I&amp;rsquo;ll go back sometime this summer and camp at Goose Island.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I want to take an Alaska cruise, but I&amp;rsquo;m worried about the volcano erupting in Anchorage.  Volcanic Ash + COPD/Asthma do not mix too well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I had a loss at the office.  I miss him terribly, but he is working at a better place now.  Good luck dude&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I had continuing &amp;ldquo;suckage&amp;rdquo; at bowling this spring.  I finished the league with a pathetic 124 average.  I started the season at 138.  Maybe this summer or fall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enough general brain &amp;ldquo;dumpage&amp;rdquo; for now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work-In-Progress:  Planter Bed</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/work-in-progress-planter-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/work-in-progress-planter-bed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The picture to the left represents my latest work-in-progress - my planter bed at the gate.  This will be for a future rose garden (it isn&amp;rsquo;t time to plant rose bushes yet in this part of Texas) in honor of my mother who passed away last April.  It isn&amp;rsquo;t done yet - I need about another 15 wheelbarrow loads of dirt from my dirt pile to fill it up, put mulch down, and plant more &amp;ldquo;plants&amp;rdquo;.  Right now, I have 5 daylilies and a few other perennial bulbs planted.  Next month, I will add three or four rose bushes from the Antique Rose Emporium and a few other perennials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The planter bed has subsurface watering via a buried soaker hose, a compost layer, and the dirt is the local &amp;ldquo;Garden Mix&amp;rdquo; that I acquired about three years ago (much better than the default Houston Black Clay).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It may not seem like much work, but it took most of the weekend to get this far.  The landscape timbers were recycled from an old bed in the back yard and had to have the pipes used to secure it removed, then be connected to each other, have two of them buried, then landscape fabric, hauling the compost from the backyard to the front, then about 35~40 wheelbarrow loads of dirt from a pile that I had to remove the grass and other junk that was growing on it (from three years ago).  In the process, got a few calluses, more than a few fire ant bites, and a few sore muscles.  But it will be worth it.  :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Update and News</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/site-update-and-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/site-update-and-news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, I have a quick update&amp;hellip;  I&amp;rsquo;ve moved the server once again - this time to my home.  I have finally been able to upgrade from my original 384K DSL to a more modern 3 MB/512KB with a static IP address, so I should be able to host from home again.  Things might be a bit slower, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t noticed many issues during the &amp;ldquo;beta&amp;rdquo; phase of the transition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also updated the software and softened the look.  Let me know what you think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More later this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009 New Years Resolutions</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/2009-new-years-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycentex.gitlab.io/blogs/2009-new-years-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, I missed my &amp;ldquo;What I Want for Christmas&amp;rdquo; post, but I will make the 2009 New Years Resolution posting before 2008 is over.  2008 has been an extremely difficult and depressing year.  I want 2009 to be a fresh start in all aspects of my life.  Thus, most of my resolutions are in the &amp;ldquo;self-help&amp;rdquo; mode and I will actually strive to follow them.  Well, first the list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Live Life in the Present and with No Regrets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep Up With Exercise and Being More Active&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn How to Relax and Not Stress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These may seem to be simple and to most people would be fairly trivial.  For me, they seem almost insurmountable.  I&amp;rsquo;ll describe below why I need to conquer these resolutions and how I intend to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Live Life in the Present with No Regrets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the hardest for me to accomplish.  I tend to live my life looking towards the past.  Thus, I let past events and mistakes haunt me.  In some ways, this explains my extreme introversion as I&amp;rsquo;m not comfortable in ever letting my guard down in fear of having to relive past regrets.  It was much more comfortable to isolate myself into the world of my own making.  Living this way is no way to exist.  I acknowledge this and thus why I want to do something to resolve this.  However, I am my own worst enemy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I wish to tackle this problem?  One tact I have recently adopted is &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t care what you think of me and what I am doing&amp;rdquo;.  This isn&amp;rsquo;t the best way to tackle this because I need to have some awareness of how I am seen or percieved of by others.  I&amp;rsquo;m using this tact to help boost my self-esteem.  After I boost my self-esteem, I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that it will encourage me to be more open.  Another thing I am trying to change is to convince myself  not to always equate every new experience to some bad memory from the past.  This behavior is causing me to retract from society and back into my shell.  Tackling this will help me live my life with no regrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been actively working on this area and I hope that some of the changes I made are showing progress.  Attending the &amp;ldquo;Live Life Like You Were Dying&amp;rdquo; sermon series at a local church this past fall has also helped give me new insights on how to live life everyday in the present and with a sense of purpose.  Also, I feel that following the second and third resolutions will help me in solving this one as they also would do more in increasing my self-worth and extroversion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep Up With Exercise and Being More Active&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m actually somewhat successful with the first half of this, but am extremely lacking on the second half of this resolution.  Ever since the event of 2008, I have made it point to exercise in some form or fashion.  I&amp;rsquo;m still starting slowly as I don&amp;rsquo;t want to jeopardize myself too much.  I started by doing short walk.  Over time, I progressed to longer walks and even some short hikes.  I now regularly do 3 to 4 mile walks with my puppy around the neighborhood and on a monthly basis take the puppy to do some of the local hikes on trails around time (I mean to do this more, but the holidays and allergies have been a detriment to me).  I want to continue to do this, and start adding some bike rides of the areas (my rear end does not like the bike seat yet&amp;hellip;).  Also, when I finish cleaning, painting, and install flooring into my old bedroom, I want to put a treadmill and a stationery bike into it along with my existing weight set.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for the second half of this resolution - the getting more active - has two sides.  One side of the getting more active is to do more things - like camping, taking trips, etc.  Most of these things I will discuss in the third resolution.  The second (and more important) side is to actually &amp;ldquo;get out and do stuff&amp;rdquo;.  At the same church that had the &amp;ldquo;Live Life Like You Were Dying&amp;rdquo;, they had a pre-Christmas message on loneliness that hit home to me.  One principle that he stressed to us was to not turn down invitations to get out and do things.  I&amp;rsquo;m known for living in my cave and not socializing with others.  This has to stop.  I&amp;rsquo;m much better at it now that I used to be, but I need to do MUCH MUCH MORE in this regards.  And even right now, I&amp;rsquo;m still ignoring an active invite, so it still is something I need to do much more work on.  Thus far, I have been relying on others to help me with this.  I still will need this help, but I also need to be more willing to try more activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus, if you have an activity you would like me to do and if it is something I would find morally or ethically acceptable, don&amp;rsquo;t take no from me as an answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn How to Relax and Not Stress&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one would definitely seem easy to most people.  I don&amp;rsquo;t relax.  I don&amp;rsquo;t turn off.  I&amp;rsquo;m serious 24 hours a day.  What I consider enjoyable most people would think of as a form of work.  I definitely need work here.  The lack of relaxation and the stress I put on myself both from work, personal issues, and from past regrets weighs heavily on my life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I do this one?  I&amp;rsquo;m hoping in going out and doing things will teach me how to relax.  I&amp;rsquo;m outdoors much more now than I have been in ages.  This has helped to relieve some stress, but it&amp;rsquo;s only a start.  That&amp;rsquo;s one of the reasons why I want to go camping, travel to places, etc.  I just need to motivate myself to just go out and do them.  For now, I&amp;rsquo;m going to go do these things myself.  Eventually, I need to find people to go do these things with.  For now, it&amp;rsquo;s just important to go do them&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do I want to do?  This is a long list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go Camping at Bastrop State Park (I have the Parks Pass)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to the Coast (Rockport)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to Enchanted Rock&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Geocache&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do the Austin Hike/Bike Trails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally go Tubing for the first time of my life&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get in the car, pick a direction, and just drive until I find something to do&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seems easy, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it&amp;hellip;  Ha&amp;hellip;  Wish me luck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S., What did I want for Christmas?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Absolution - Something no person on earth can give me, but what I already have.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assurance - See absolution Above&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forgiveness - I am striving to forgive anyone who has aggrieved me over the years and all I want from others is their forgiveness for any and everything I may have done.  I don&amp;rsquo;t always perceive when I wrong someone and I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for that&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>